{
   "borrowerData": [
	{
		"id": 269,
		"title": "Ms.",
		"firstName": "Devina",
		"lastName": "Raj",
		"email": "convallis.erat.eget@arcu.co.uk",
		"mobile": "+91 0824986780",
		"password": "IER76WOI6QG",
		"amount": 324500,
		"interestRate": 19,
		"tenure": 29,
		"loanPurpose": "Relocation",
		"dateOfBirth": "March 15th, 2002",
		"highestEducation": "Graduate",
		"maritalStatus": "Never Married",
		"spouseName": "Kandhara",
		"fatherName": "Lohitaksha",
		"dependents": 3,
		"residenceType": "Rented House - Living alone",
		"address1": "P.O. Box 729, 368 Blandit Road",
		"address2": "Ap #847-7159 In Street",
		"city": "Hazaribag",
		"state": "Jharkhand",
		"country": "India",
		"zipCode": "580601",
		"cityDuration": 22,
		"residenceDuration": 5,
		"alternatePhone": "+91 7405345527",
		"panNumber": "HWRQS3460J",
		"employmentType": "Salaried",
		"companyName": "Cubilia Curae; Phasellus Ltd",
		"designation": "condimentum",
		"totalYears": 14,
		"totalMonths": 8,
		"currentYears": 5,
		"currentMonths": 9,
		"monthlyTakeHome": 26079,
		"monthlyEMIs": 16595,
		"investedMarkets": false,
		"investedProperty": true,
		"accountName": "Someshwar",
		"accountNumber": "5393895398034980",
		"bankName": "malesuada",
		"accountType": "Current",
		"bankIFSC": "KGTU6251376",
		"bankBranch": "P.O. Box 108, 9019 Vel Avenue",
		"cibilScore": 426,
		"profileImage": "a",
		"panCardFront": "Quisque",
		"panCardBack": "non",
		"passportFront": "fringilla",
		"passportBack": "hendrerit",
		"aadharFront": "natoque",
		"aadharBack": "nibh.",
		"voterIDFront": "a,",
		"voterIDBack": "fermentum",
		"rentalAgreement": "auctor",
		"electricityBill": "augue",
		"mobileBill": "mauris,",
		"itrFY1": "non",
		"itrFY2": "Morbi",
		"itrFY3": "tellus",
		"salarySlip1": "scelerisque",
		"salarySlip2": "ultricies",
		"salarySlip3": "id",
		"bankStatement": "risus,",
		"creditCardStatement": "sit",
		"featuredCountry": false,
		"featuredCity": true
	},
	{
		"id": 892,
		"title": "Mr.",
		"firstName": "Trinayani",
		"lastName": "Jain",
		"email": "ornare.tortor.at@loremeget.org",
		"mobile": "+91 6091711940",
		"password": "AXW64WEF4TQ",
		"amount": 347033,
		"interestRate": 14,
		"tenure": 36,
		"loanPurpose": "Home Improvement",
		"dateOfBirth": "August 5th, 1950",
		"highestEducation": "Undergraduate",
		"maritalStatus": " Widowed",
		"spouseName": "Abhinithi",
		"fatherName": "Sudhindra",
		"dependents": 2,
		"residenceType": "Own House - Living with family",
		"address1": "P.O. Box 206, 3879 Condimentum. St.",
		"address2": "6383 Molestie Street",
		"city": "Kavaratti",
		"state": "LD",
		"country": "India",
		"zipCode": "950699",
		"cityDuration": 36,
		"residenceDuration": 24,
		"alternatePhone": "+91 7823179624",
		"panNumber": "GOSBH8945G",
		"employmentType": "Business",
		"companyName": "Tellus Aenean Corporation",
		"designation": "arcu.",
		"totalYears": 39,
		"totalMonths": 10,
		"currentYears": 28,
		"currentMonths": 3,
		"monthlyTakeHome": 41432,
		"monthlyEMIs": 92642,
		"investedMarkets": true,
		"investedProperty": false,
		"accountName": "Grhalakshmi",
		"accountNumber": "5136052087164882",
		"bankName": "Cum",
		"accountType": "Loan",
		"bankIFSC": "OMUD2111968",
		"bankBranch": "6963 Donec Rd.",
		"cibilScore": 807,
		"profileImage": "fames",
		"panCardFront": "nunc",
		"panCardBack": "risus.",
		"passportFront": "nisl.",
		"passportBack": "nascetur",
		"aadharFront": "amet,",
		"aadharBack": "ac,",
		"voterIDFront": "Nam",
		"voterIDBack": "posuere",
		"rentalAgreement": "molestie",
		"electricityBill": "commodo",
		"mobileBill": "eget",
		"itrFY1": "ipsum.",
		"itrFY2": "amet",
		"itrFY3": "nulla.",
		"salarySlip1": "semper",
		"salarySlip2": "dui.",
		"salarySlip3": "augue",
		"bankStatement": "mollis.",
		"creditCardStatement": "sociosqu",
		"featuredCountry": true,
		"featuredCity": true
	},
	{
		"id": 727,
		"title": "",
		"firstName": "Baladhitya",
		"lastName": "Ismail",
		"email": "risus@nisia.com",
		"mobile": "+91 0112384193",
		"password": "CSC34LXG4XT",
		"amount": 394077,
		"interestRate": 14,
		"tenure": 28,
		"loanPurpose": "Medical",
		"dateOfBirth": "September 30th, 1956",
		"highestEducation": "Graduate",
		"maritalStatus": "Married",
		"spouseName": "Chidambar",
		"fatherName": "Vijay",
		"dependents": 1,
		"residenceType": "Rented House - Living with friends",
		"address1": "696-1692 Donec Avenue",
		"address2": "P.O. Box 324, 4884 Tincidunt Rd.",
		"city": "Bhubaneswar",
		"state": "OR",
		"country": "India",
		"zipCode": "386414",
		"cityDuration": 36,
		"residenceDuration": 12,
		"alternatePhone": "+91 5747803156",
		"panNumber": "FEBOQ9447F",
		"employmentType": "Salaried",
		"companyName": "Et Lacinia Vitae Ltd",
		"designation": "ultrices sit",
		"totalYears": 23,
		"totalMonths": 7,
		"currentYears": 3,
		"currentMonths": 1,
		"monthlyTakeHome": 10877,
		"monthlyEMIs": 60176,
		"investedMarkets": false,
		"investedProperty": true,
		"accountName": "Najma",
		"accountNumber": "5446848641544682",
		"bankName": "vitae",
		"accountType": "Current",
		"bankIFSC": "QJLQ8684382",
		"bankBranch": "686-7945 Sapien, Rd.",
		"cibilScore": 483,
		"profileImage": "feugiat",
		"panCardFront": "diam",
		"panCardBack": "id,",
		"passportFront": "congue,",
		"passportBack": "vel,",
		"aadharFront": "enim",
		"aadharBack": "facilisis",
		"voterIDFront": "hendrerit",
		"voterIDBack": "mollis.",
		"rentalAgreement": "primis",
		"electricityBill": "nibh.",
		"mobileBill": "magna.",
		"itrFY1": "ac",
		"itrFY2": "Nunc",
		"itrFY3": "Nullam",
		"salarySlip1": "auctor,",
		"salarySlip2": "dictum",
		"salarySlip3": "cubilia",
		"bankStatement": "vehicula",
		"creditCardStatement": "non",
		"featuredCountry": true,
		"featuredCity": false
	},
	{
		"id": 257,
		"title": "",
		"firstName": "Nalin",
		"lastName": "Patel",
		"email": "adipiscing@AeneanmassaInteger.org",
		"mobile": "+91 8766245884",
		"password": "HQM79IPU4SR",
		"amount": 404479,
		"interestRate": 17,
		"tenure": 12,
		"loanPurpose": "Debt Consolidation",
		"dateOfBirth": "April 8th, 1968",
		"highestEducation": "Graduate",
		"maritalStatus": "Married",
		"spouseName": "Aadesh",
		"fatherName": "Meghdutt",
		"dependents": 2,
		"residenceType": "Own House - Living alone",
		"address1": "Ap #615-8686 Sed Av.",
		"address2": "P.O. Box 424, 2710 Eu, Road",
		"city": "Ajmer",
		"state": "RJ",
		"country": "India",
		"zipCode": "240329",
		"cityDuration": 40,
		"residenceDuration": 6,
		"alternatePhone": "+91 6668440200",
		"panNumber": "TVZHJ0858C",
		"employmentType": "Business",
		"companyName": "Ac Feugiat Non Limited",
		"designation": "lectus.",
		"totalYears": 43,
		"totalMonths": 2,
		"currentYears": 41,
		"currentMonths": 5,
		"monthlyTakeHome": 52811,
		"monthlyEMIs": 33954,
		"investedMarkets": true,
		"investedProperty": false,
		"accountName": "Lalit",
		"accountNumber": "5578738164278539",
		"bankName": "mauris. Morbi non",
		"accountType": "Deposit",
		"bankIFSC": "JZYA6562919",
		"bankBranch": "Ap #867-3228 Vitae, Street",
		"cibilScore": 379,
		"profileImage": "vulputate,",
		"panCardFront": "consectetuer",
		"panCardBack": "ultrices.",
		"passportFront": "nec,",
		"passportBack": "Duis",
		"aadharFront": "purus",
		"aadharBack": "auctor",
		"voterIDFront": "interdum",
		"voterIDBack": "orci.",
		"rentalAgreement": "Fusce",
		"electricityBill": "Donec",
		"mobileBill": "tincidunt",
		"itrFY1": "non,",
		"itrFY2": "et",
		"itrFY3": "nonummy",
		"salarySlip1": "metus.",
		"salarySlip2": "eu,",
		"salarySlip3": "scelerisque",
		"bankStatement": "libero.",
		"creditCardStatement": "a,",
		"featuredCountry": true,
		"featuredCity": false
	},
	{
		"id": 208,
		"title": "Ms.",
		"firstName": "Hassan",
		"lastName": "Khan",
		"email": "faucibus.orci.luctus@faucibusorci.edu",
		"mobile": "+91 3538385508",
		"password": "SIW50FBR9XA",
		"amount": 12013,
		"interestRate": 17,
		"tenure": 15,
		"loanPurpose": "Home Improvement",
		"dateOfBirth": "January 10th, 2000",
		"highestEducation": "Post Graduate",
		"maritalStatus": " Widowed",
		"spouseName": "Someshwar",
		"fatherName": "Nalin",
		"dependents": 1,
		"residenceType": "Rented House - Living with friends",
		"address1": "2651 Justo Rd.",
		"address2": "P.O. Box 605, 8416 Hendrerit. St.",
		"city": "Port Blair",
		"state": "Andaman and Nicobar Islands",
		"country": "India",
		"zipCode": "178178",
		"cityDuration": 31,
		"residenceDuration": 47,
		"alternatePhone": "+91 5339567500",
		"panNumber": "PTQRE6122K",
		"employmentType": "Business",
		"companyName": "Ultrices Vivamus Rhoncus Ltd",
		"designation": "luctus",
		"totalYears": 24,
		"totalMonths": 8,
		"currentYears": 32,
		"currentMonths": 1,
		"monthlyTakeHome": 87339,
		"monthlyEMIs": 51023,
		"investedMarkets": false,
		"investedProperty": false,
		"accountName": "Hafiz",
		"accountNumber": "5307555173045446",
		"bankName": "lobortis",
		"accountType": "Savings",
		"bankIFSC": "IJPJ4279752",
		"bankBranch": "9744 Bibendum. St.",
		"cibilScore": 624,
		"profileImage": "vestibulum",
		"panCardFront": "et,",
		"panCardBack": "risus.",
		"passportFront": "sem",
		"passportBack": "dictum.",
		"aadharFront": "Nunc",
		"aadharBack": "Duis",
		"voterIDFront": "non,",
		"voterIDBack": "nec",
		"rentalAgreement": "augue",
		"electricityBill": "massa",
		"mobileBill": "mollis.",
		"itrFY1": "tincidunt",
		"itrFY2": "nec",
		"itrFY3": "lacus.",
		"salarySlip1": "Nunc",
		"salarySlip2": "auctor",
		"salarySlip3": "mattis",
		"bankStatement": "enim.",
		"creditCardStatement": "Donec",
		"featuredCountry": false,
		"featuredCity": true
	}
]
}